Guide to the Albrecht Goetze Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory, 1923-1971; 8.25; (22 boxes)
  - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1947, 1950, 1956, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 411)
  - Pinches, Theophilus G., 1928 (Box 16, Folder 411)
  - Platt, Edward J.(*), 1954-1961, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 412-413)
  - Platt, Katherine B. (Mrs. T. Beach), 1949 (Box 16, Folder 414)
  - Poebel, Arno, 1926, 1936-1947 (Box 16, Folder 414)
  - Pohl, P.A.(*), 1932-1940, 1944-1947 (Box 16, Folder 415-416)
  - Pohl, P.A.(*), 1950-1961, undated (Box 16, Folder 417)
  - Polanyi, Karl, 1955 (Box 16, Folder 418)
  - Polomé, Edgar G.C., 1956, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 418)
  - Polotsky, Hans Jakob, 1951-1954, 1959-1964 (Box 16, Folder 418)
  - Pope, Liston, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 418)
  - Pope, Marvin H.(*), 1941-1949 (Box 16, Folder 419)
  - Porada, Edith(*), 1939-1950 (Box 17, Folder 420-422)
  - Porada, Edith(*), 1939-1950 (Box 17, Folder 423)
  - Posener, Georges, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - Post, B. von, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - Pottle, Frederick A., 1943 (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - Price, Derek J. de S., undated (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - Princeton University, 1941, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 424)
  - Princeton University, The Library, 1953-1959 (Box 17, Folder 425)
  - Princeton University Press, 1949-1955 (Box 17, Folder 425)
  - Printz, Wilhelm, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 425)
  - Pritchard, James B.(*), 1944-1948 (Box 17, Folder 426)
  - Pritchard, James B., 1949-1950, 1952-1956 (Box 17, Folder 427-428)
  - Pritchard, James B.(*), 1957-1959, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 429)
  - Pritsch, Erich, 1953, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 430)
  - Proosdij, Boris Antonius van, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 430)
  - Proskauer, Curt, 1961, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 430)
  - Przeworski, Stefan(*), 1925-1929 (Box 17, Folder 430)
  - Przeworski, Stefan(*), 1930-1940 (Box 17, Folder 431)
  - Puhvel, Jaan, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 432)
  - Purves, Pierre M., 1941-1947 (Box 17, Folder 432)
  - Pye, Ernest, 1940-1951 (Box 17, Folder 432)
  - Rabinowitz, Louis M., 1952-1953 (Box 17, Folder 433)
  - Ramsay, William M., 1931 (Box 17, Folder 433)
  - Ranke, Hermann(*), 1930-1946 (Box 17, Folder 433)
  - Ranoschek, Ergebenst, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Rapp, Franz, 1937, undated (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Rauchenbichler, Josef, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Ravn, O.E., 1934-1936, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Ray, Erwin R., 1962 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Reade, Julian, 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Redden, James E., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Redford, Donald B., 1962 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Reed, William L., undated (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Reichardt, Konstantin, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 434)
  - Reichenberger, Arnold, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 435)
  - Reidemeister, Kurt
    See: box 14, folder 350
  - Reiner, Erica, 1953, 1960-1970 (Box 17, Folder 435)
  - Reitzenstein, Richard, 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 435)
  - Renard, Marcel, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 435)
  - Rencontre Assyriologique Internationale, 1965-1967 (Box 17, Folder 436)
  - Renov, Israel, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 436)
  - Rescher, Oscar, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 436)
  - Reschid, Fauzi, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - Revue Hittite et Asianique, 1933-1941 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - "Rhino"
    See: box 19, folder 492-493
  - Riccobono, Salvatore, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - Rice, Michael, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - Richardson, H. Neil, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - Richies, S., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - Riedel, Wilhelm, 1950-1953 (Box 17, Folder 437)
  - Riemen, William P., 1960 (Box 17, Folder 438)
  - Riemschneider, Kaspar K., 1961 (Box 17, Folder 438)
  - Riemschneider, Margarete, 1952, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 438)
  - Riftin, Aleksandr Pavlovich, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 438)
  - Rigg, Horace A., Jr.(*), 1935-1937 (Box 17, Folder 439)
  - Rigg, Horace A., Jr.(*), 1938-1940 (Box 17, Folder 440)
  - Rivisti degli Studi Orientali, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 440)
  - Roberts, Jimmy J.M., 1970 (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - Rockwell, Kiffin A., undated (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - Rodenwaldt, Gerhart, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - Roeder, Günther, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - Röllig, Wolfgang, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - Rössler, Otto, 1953 (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - Rohde, Georg, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 441)
  - Romanoff, Paul, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 442)
  - Rosenkranz, Bernhard(*), 1936, 1939, 1947-1957 (Box 17, Folder 442)
  - Rosenow, Edith, 1942-1947 (Box 17, Folder 443)
  - Rosenthal, Franz, 1939-1940, 1954, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 443)
  - Rost, Liane, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 443)
  - Rostovtzeff, Michael, 1934-1942 (Box 17, Folder 443)
  - Rowley, Harold H.(*), 1946-1962 (Box 17, Folder 444)
  - Rowton, M.B., 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 444)
  - Royal Ontario Museum of Archaeology, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 444)
  - Rudolph, Wilhelm, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 444)
  - Rüstow, Alexander, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 445)
  - Rundgren, Fritjof, 1954-1955 (Box 17, Folder 445)
  - Russell, J.C., 1961 (Box 17, Folder 445)
  - Ryckmans, Gonzague, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 445)
  - Saarisalo, Aapeli, 1946 (Box 17, Folder 445)
  - Sabeh, Joseph, 1950 (Box 17, Folder 445)
  - Sachs, Abraham(*), 1936-1945 April-Dec, 1946 January-July (Box 17, Folder 446-451)
  - Sachs, Abraham(*), 1946 August-Dec, 1947 January-Sep, 1947 November-Dec, 1948, 1950-1969, undated (Box 18, Folder 452-461)
  - Sachs, Benjamin, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 462)
  - Safrastian, Arshak, 1942-1954 (Box 18, Folder 462)
  - Saggs, Henry William Frederick, 1959-1960 (Box 18, Folder 462)
  - Saint Louis, City Art Museum, 1951, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 462)
  - Salinger, Gerhard, 1971, undated (Box 18, Folder 462)
  - Salonen, Armas, 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 463)
  - San Nicolò, Mariano, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 463)
  - Sapir, Edward, 1936-1938, undated (Box 18, Folder 463)
  - Sarton, George, [1952?] (Box 18, Folder 463)
  - Sayce, Archibald Henry, 1928-1931 (Box 18, Folder 463)
  - Schachermeyr, Fritz(*), 1925-1934, 1959-1963 (Box 18, Folder 464)
  - Schacht, Joseph, 1928-1929 (Box 18, Folder 465)
  - Schaeder, Hans H., 1924-1930, 1939 (Box 18, Folder 465)
  - Schaeffer, Claude F. A., 1948-1959, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 465)
  - Schall, Anton, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 466)
  - Scharff, Alexander, 1932, 1934, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 466)
  - Schaum, Harvey, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 466)
  - Schaumberger, Johannes, 1946, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 466)
  - Schayer, Stanislaus, 1938 (Box 18, Folder 466)
  - Schayer, ____, 1923 (Box 18, Folder 466)
  - Schede, Martin(*), 1925-1933 (Box 18, Folder 467)
  - Scheel, Helmuth, 1932, 1952, 1963-1967, undated (Box 18, Folder 468)
  - Schehl, Franz, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 468)
  - Schencke, Wilhelm, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 468)
  - Scherman, Lucian(*), 1932, 1939, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 469)
  - Scherman, Richard P., 1938, 1946 (Box 18, Folder 469)
  - Schloessinger, Miriam S. (Mrs. Max), 1942 (Box 18, Folder 470)
  - Schmidtke, Friedrich R., 1929, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 470)
  - Schmökel, Hartmut, 1931, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 470)
  - Schneider, Nikolaus, 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 470)
  - Schoch, Paul, 1926 (Box 18, Folder 470)
  - Schorr, Moses, 1928 (Box 18, Folder 471)
  - Schott, Siegfried, 1929-1930, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 471)
  - Schove, D. Justin, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 471)
  - Schrijver, Adolf L., 1950 (Box 18, Folder 471)
  - Schröder, F.R., 1926-1927 (Box 18, Folder 471)
  - Schubert, ____ von, 1929-1930 (Box 18, Folder 472)
  - Schuler, Einar von(*), 1954-1968 (Box 18, Folder 472)
  - Schulman, Alan R., 1960 (Box 18, Folder 473)
  - Schuster, Hans-Siegfried, 1957-1963, undated (Box 18, Folder 473)
  - Schwartz, Benjamin, 1937-1941, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 473)
  - Schweitzer, Cathy (Mrs. C.E.), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 473)
  - Scott, Donald, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 473)
  - Seemann, Curt H., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 474)
  - Semper, Max, 1927, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 474)
  - Senyürek, Muzaffer S., 1946, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 474)
  - Seters, [A.J.C.?] van, undated (Box 18, Folder 474)
  - Ševoroškin, V., 1964 (Box 18, Folder 474)
  - Seyrig, Henri, 1948-1968 (Box 18, Folder 475)
  - Shafer, Robert, 1940, 1945, 1959-1962 (Box 18, Folder 475)
  - Shaffer, Aaron, 1961, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 475)
  - Shepard, Frederic W., 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 475)
  - Shileiko, V.K., 1928 (Box 18, Folder 475)
  - Sieg, Emil H., 1930, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 475)
  - Silk, Edmund T., 1959 (Box 18, Folder 475)
  - Simmons, Stephen D.(*), 1954-1963, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 476)
  - Simpson, William K.(*), 1951-1958 (Box 18, Folder 477)
  - Singer, A.D., 1943, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 478)
  - Sinor, Denis, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 478)
  - Sinnott, Edmund W., 1951 (Box 18, Folder 478)
  - Sjöberg, Åke W., 1967, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 478)
  - Skaggs, Scherry, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 479)
  - Slotty, Friedrich, [post-1938] (Box 18, Folder 479)
  - Smick, Elmer B., 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 479)
  - Smith, C.C., 1947, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 479)
  - Smith, Morton, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 480)
  - Smith, Robert H., 1958-1959, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 480)
  - Smith, Sidney(*), 1925-1949, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 481)
  - Smith, W.S., 1959 (Box 18, Folder 481)
  - Smith College, 1944-1957 (Box 18, Folder 482)
  - Smither, Mary P., 1966 (Box 18, Folder 482)
  - Snyder, John W., 1955 (Box 18, Folder 482)
  - Sobernheim, N., 1927-1930 (Box 18, Folder 483)
  - Societas Linguistica Europaea, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 483)
  - Société Asiatique de Paris, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 483)
  - Society for the Protection of Science and Learning, 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 483)
  - Soden, Wolfram von, 1950, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 484)
  - Sollberger, Edmond(*), 1949-1953 (Box 18, Folder 484)
  - Sollberger, Edmond(*), 1954-1969, 1924-1940, 1946-1962 (Box 19, Folder 485-487)
  - Sommer, Ferdinand(*), 1924-1931, 1932-1940, 1946-1952, 1953-1962 (Box 19, Folder 488-490)
  - Sommer, Robert, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 491)
  - Sommerfelt, Alf, 1960 (Box 19, Folder 491)
  - Soucek, Vladimir, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 491)
  - Southern Baptist Theological Seminary, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 491)
  - Southworth, Franklin C., 1957 (Box 19, Folder 491)
  - Spain, Consejo Superior de Investigaciones Cientificas, Instituto de Pedagogia, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 491)
  - Speers, Nellie D. (Mrs. James M.), 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 491)
  - Speiser, Ephraim A.(*), 1935-1938 March (Box 19, Folder 492-493)
  - Speiser, Ephraim A., 1938 April-Dec, 1939 January-September (Box 19, Folder 494-497)
  - Speiser, Ephraim A.(*), 1939 October-1940 March-Dec, 1941-1960 (Box 19, Folder 498-506)
  - Speiser, Ephraim A.(*), 1960-1964 (Box 19, Folder 498-507)
  - Speleers, Louis, 1946-1948 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - Spiegelberg, Wilhelm, 1924, 1930 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - Sprengling, Martin, 1935-1938 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - Stamires, George A., 1953 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - Stamm, Johann Jakob, 1939, 1946 (Box 19, Folder 508)
  - Stang, Fredrik(*), 1934-1936 (Box 19, Folder 509)
  - Stanislawski, Dan, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Stanton, Ida D. (Mrs. C.A.), 1942 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Stearns, John B.(*), 1953-1960 (Box 19, Folder 510)
  - Stech, Tamara
    See: box 20, folder 536
  - Steele, Francis F., 1942-1952, 1962, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Steinherr, Franz, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Steinthal, Walter, 1938-1941 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Stengel, Edmund, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 511)
  - Stephens, Ferris J.(*), 1935-1948, 1956-1960 (Box 19, Folder 512)
  - Stern, Harry L., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Stichel, Rainer, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Stinespring, William F., 1940 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Stokes, Pat, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Stoltenberg, Hans L., 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Stone, A.P., 1961 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Straller, Ilse, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Strang, Carl J., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 513)
  - Strommenger, Eva, 1957-1961, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 514)
  - Struve, Vasiliĭ V., 1946, undated (Box 20, Folder 514)
  - Sturm, Josef, 1934-1935 (Box 20, Folder 514)
  - Sturtevant, Edgar H.(*), 1928-1939, 1949, n.d (Box 20, Folder 515)
  - Sükrü M., 1934 (Box 20, Folder 515)
  - Sukenik, Yigael, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 516)
  - Sundwall, Johannes, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 516)
  - Swadesh, Morris, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 516)
  - Szemerényi, Oswald J.L., 1965, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 516)
  - Szlechter, Emile, 1952-1956 (Box 20, Folder 516)
  - Tadmor, Hayim, 1957-1958 (Box 20, Folder 517)
  - Tallgren, Aarne M., 1933-1938 (Box 20, Folder 517)
  - Tavadia, Jehangir C., 1926, 1935, undated (Box 20, Folder 518)
  - Taylor, Diane E., 1966, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 518)
  - Tedesco, Paul, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 518)
  - Teleki, Suzanne, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 518)
  - Tenner, Ernst, 1926, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 518)
  - Thiel, ____, 1930, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 519)
  - Thiele, Edwin R., 1949 (Box 20, Folder 519)
  - Thomas, Homer L., 1966 (Box 20, Folder 519)
  - Thompson, Reginald Campbell, 1925-1926, 1935 (Box 20, Folder 519)
  - Thorson, Playford V., 1964 (Box 20, Folder 519)
  - Thureau-Dangin, François, 1933-1939 (Box 20, Folder 519)
  - Tiera, John C., 1950 (Box 20, Folder 520)
  - Tietz, John W., 1954 (Box 20, Folder 520)
  - Tipple, Bertrand Martin, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 520)
  - Toledo, Demetrio de, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 520)
  - Tomory, Susan, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 520)
  - Torrey, Charles C., 1939-1954 (Box 20, Folder 520)
  - Toynbee, Arnold(*), 1951-1954 (Box 20, Folder 521)
  - Traylor, John H., Jr., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 522)
  - Trever, John C., 1950-1953 (Box 20, Folder 522)
  - Troeltsch, ____, 1930, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 522)
  - Trokay, Madeleine, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 522)
  - Trutmann, Albertine, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 522)
  - Trutmann, [H.?], 1967 (Box 20, Folder 522)
  - Tseretheli, M.(*), 1927-1935 (Box 20, Folder 523)
  - Tsevat, Matitiahu, 1954-1959 (Box 20, Folder 523)
  - Tucker, Gene M., 1966 (Box 20, Folder 524)
  - Türk Tarih:Kurumu
  - Turkey, Director General of Antiquities and Museums, 1936-1937, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 524)
  - Turkey, Ministry of Education, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 524)
  - Turkish Historical Society
  - Unger, Eckard O., 1929,1932 (Box 20, Folder 524)
  - Ungnad, Arthur, 1925, 1931-1936 (Box 20, Folder 524)
  - U.S.S.R. Society for Cultural Relations with Foreign Countries, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 524)
  - United States, Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 525)
  - United States, Department of State, 1945-1948 (Box 20, Folder 525)
    See also: box 2, folder 28-50 See also: box 10, folder 239-247
  - United States, Foreign Service, American Embassy, Ankara, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 525)
    See also: box 3, folder 52-53 See also: box 20, folder 525
  - United States, Foreign Service, American Embassy, Baghdad
  - University of Toronto Quarterly, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 526)
  - Upadhye, Adinath N., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 526)
  - Urgell, J., 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 526)
  - Ussishkin, D., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 526)
  - Van Buren, Elizabeth Douglas, 1936-1938, 1948-1955 (Box 20, Folder 527)
  - Vandemeulebroucke, Robert, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 527)
  - Van Norman, Louis E., 1938 (Box 20, Folder 527)
  - Vaux, Roland de, 1938, 1940, 1954, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 527)
  - Velikovsky, Immanuel, 1947-1952 (Box 20, Folder 528)
  - Verlag Gebr. Mann, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 528)
  - Vester, John T., 1957 (Box 20, Folder 528)
  - Vieyra, Maurice, 1947-1955 (Box 20, Folder 528)
  - Vine, Kenneth, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 529)
  - Virroleaud, Charles, 1937-1938, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 529)
  - Vogel, Kurt, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 529)
  - Vogelstein, Max, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 529)
  - Volterra, Edouard, 1940-1941 (Box 20, Folder 529)
  - Vorys, Jeanny E.
    See: box 4, folder 98
  - Vrouyr, Norayr E., 1948, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 529)
  - Vycichl, W., 1949 (Box 20, Folder 529)
  - Wach, Joachim, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Wadewitz, Bertha, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Waerden, Bartel L. van der, 1947, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Wagner, A., 1932 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Wait, Peter, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Wallinga, Herman Tammo, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Walser, Gerold, 1962-1964, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 530)
  - Walters, Stanley D., 1963-1968 (Box 20, Folder 531)
  - Walters Art Gallery, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 531)
  - Walther, Arnold, 1925, 1931-1938 (Box 20, Folder 531)
  - Ware, ____, 1940 (Box 20, Folder 531)
  - Wasserman, Felix, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 532)
  - Waterman, Leroy, 1938-1959, undated (Box 20, Folder 532)
  - Watson, B.A., 1951 (Box 20, Folder 532)
  - Weber, Otto, 1924-1925 (Box 20, Folder 532)
  - Weber, Wilhelm, 1925, undated (Box 20, Folder 532)
  - Weidenreich, Franz, 1932, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 533)
  - Weidner, Ernst F.(*), 1928-1934, 1939, 1947-1962 (Box 20, Folder 533)
  - Weigand, Hermann J., 1934 (Box 20, Folder 534)
  - Weigle, Luther A., 1945-1946 (Box 20, Folder 534)
  - Weil, Gerard E., 1954 (Box 20, Folder 534)
  - Weinreich, Otto, 1925, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 534)
  - Weir, Cecil J. Mullo, 1946 (Box 20, Folder 535)
  - Weiss, J.G., 1930 (Box 20, Folder 535)
  - Weiss, P.F.D., 1960 (Box 20, Folder 535)
  - Welles, Charles B., 1936, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 535)
  - Wenger, Leopold, 1938-1939 (Box 20, Folder 536)
  - Werner, Rudolf, 1949-1954, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 536)
  - Wetzel, Friedrich, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 536)
  - Wheeler, Tamara S., undated (Box 20, Folder 536)
  - White, William, Jr., 1965 (Box 20, Folder 537)
  - Whitehouse, Elizabeth, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 537)
  - Whittemore, Thomas, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 537)
  - Who's Who in America, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 537)
  - Wiegand, Theodor, 1926 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Wikander, Stig, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Wilcken, Ulrich, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Wilheim, Gernot, 1946, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Wilkinson, Charles K., 1955, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Willey, Gordon R., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Williams, R.J., 1947-1952 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Williams College, 1951 (Box 20, Folder 538)
  - Wilson, John A.(*), 1937-1946, 1951,1961, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 539)
  - Winckworth, C.P.T., 1946 (Box 20, Folder 539)
  - Winnett, Fred V., 1952-1956 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Carl Winter's Universitätsbuchhandlung, 1936, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Wisconsin, University of, 1952-1955 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Wisconsin, University of--Milwaukee, 1961-1962 (Box 20, Folder 540)
  - Wiseman, Donald J.(*), 1951-1954, 1956-1970 (Box 20, Folder 541-543)
  - Wissenschaftliche Buchgesellschaft, 1963-1970, undated (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Wittmann, ____, undated (Box 20, Folder 544)
  - Wohlstein, Hermann, 1951, 1956-1957 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - Wolf, Herbert M., 1966 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - Word, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 545)
  - World Congress of Jewish Studies in Jerusalem, 1960, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 546)
  - Wrathall, Donald S., 1959-1962 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Wright, George Ernest(*), 1955-1960, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Wright, Harry N., 1947 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Wyer, Samuel S., 1949 (Box 20, Folder 547)
  - Yacoubian, Adour H., 1941 (Box 21, Folder 548)
  - Yahuda, Abraham Shalom, 1942 (Box 21, Folder 548)
  - Yale College, Dean, 1951, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 548)
  - Yale Faculty Club, 1956, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 549)
  - Yale University Art Gallery, 1935, 1942, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 549)
  - Yale University, Babylonian Collection
    See: box 9, folder 210 See: box 19, folder 512
  - Yale University, Department of Classics, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 549)
  - Yale University, Department of Oriental Studies, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 549)
  - Yale University, Department of Religion, 1939, 1942, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 549)
  - Yale University, Divinity School, 1953, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 549)
    See also: box 20, folder 534
  - Yale University, Division of Engineering and New Construction, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 549)
  - Yale University, Graduate School, 1938, 1964, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 550)
  - Yale University Library, 1949, 1958, 1965, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 550)
  - Yale University News Bureau, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 550)
  - Yale University, President
    See: box 3, folder 56 See: box 8, folder 193
  - Yale University, President and Fellows, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 550)
  - Yale University Press, 1940, 1947, 1957, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 551)
  - Yale University, Provost, 1947, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 551)
  - Yale University, Secretary, 1952 (Box 21, Folder 551)
  - Yale University, Treasurer, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 551)
  - Yaron, Reuven, [1953?] (Box 21, Folder 551)
  - Young, George Douglas, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 551)
  - Zachariah, George K., 1967 (Box 21, Folder 552)
  - Zacharow, A., 1929 (Box 21, Folder 552)
  - Zahn, Robert, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 552)
  - Zgusta, Ladislav, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 552)
  - Zimmer, Heinrich, 1934-1937 (Box 21, Folder 552)
  - Zimmer, Heinrich(*), 1938-1941 (Box 21, Folder 553)
  - Zimmern, Heinrich, 1924-1930 (Box 21, Folder 554)
  - Zübeyr, Hamit, 1931-1932 (Box 21, Folder 554)
  - Zuntz, Günther, 1945 (Box 21, Folder 555)
  - Zuntz, Leonie(*), 1932-1934 (Box 21, Folder 555)
  - Zuntz, Leonie, 1935-1938 (Box 21, Folder 556)
  - Zyhlarz, Ernst, 1937 (Box 21, Folder 556)
  - Unidentified incoming, 1924-1970, undated (Box 21, Folder 557)
  - Unidentified outgoing, 1928-1936, undated (Box 21, Folder 558)
  - Greeting cards, 1966-1969, undated (Box 21, Folder 559)
  - Notes, drafts, and transcriptions, undated (Box 21, Folder 560)
  - Recommendations
    Conditions Governing Access
    Letters of recomendation for students and colleagues written by Albrecht Goetze between 1958 and 1971 are restricted for seventy-five years or until 2047.
    - A-G (Box 22, Folder 561)
    - H (Box 22, Folder 562)
    - J-M (Box 22, Folder 563)
    - P (Box 22, Folder 564)
    - R-S (Box 22, Folder 565)
    - T-Z (Box 22, Folder 566)
      Note: see page 11 for restrictions on access to Box 22.